{
    "id": "753c66e80c7a43989b70e97c4ce16b5b",
    "title": "No and Not",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "654b7de323fc49c7a0ebe2720c7f667d",
            "title": "No And Not",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………… all birds can sing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "Not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can meet you today, but ………………….. on Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I sent her several letters, but received …………….. reply.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is a …………………. parking area.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is certainly ………………….. the most talented person in the team.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was …………………. at all amused.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ………………… children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. two people are alike.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Not",
                        "No"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… surprisingly, he failed the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "Not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was ………………… much we could do to help.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}